var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "And the earth",
        "pcklId": "455",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْلَى",
        "answer": "will be tested",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "tub'lā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "bayni",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالتَّرَائِبِ",
        "answer": "and the ribs",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-tarāibi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الثَّاقِبُ",
        "answer": "the piercing",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-thāqibu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَافِظٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a protector",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ḥāfiẓun",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُ",
        "answer": "Coming forth",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "yakhruju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلِقَ",
        "answer": "he is created",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "khuliqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلِقَ",
        "answer": "He is created",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "khuliqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرَاكَ",
        "answer": "can make you know",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "adrāka",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَافِقٍ",
        "answer": "ejected",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "dāfiqin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجْعِهِ",
        "answer": "return him",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "rajʿihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّجْعِ",
        "answer": "returns",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-rajʿi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُوَيْدًا",
        "answer": "little",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "ruwaydan",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّرَائِرُ",
        "answer": "the secrets",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-sarāiru",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "By the sky",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "wal-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "By the sky",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "wal-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّدْعِ",
        "answer": "cracks open",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ṣadʿi",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّلْبِ",
        "answer": "the backbone",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-ṣul'bi",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالطَّارِقِ",
        "answer": "and the night comer",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wal-ṭāriqi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّارِقُ",
        "answer": "the night comer (is)",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-ṭāriqu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصْلٌ",
        "answer": "decisive",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "faṣlun",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَادِرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Able",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "laqādirun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَوْلٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a Word",
        "pcklId": "1716",
        "tlit": "laqawlun",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُوَّةٍ",
        "answer": "power",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "quwwatin",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "512",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "(is) every",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "are plotting",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yakīdūna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكِيدُ",
        "answer": "But I am planning",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-akīdu",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدًا",
        "answer": "a plot",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "kaydan",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدًا",
        "answer": "a plan",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "kaydan",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَهِّلِ",
        "answer": "So give respite",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "famahhili",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْهِلْهُمْ",
        "answer": "Give respite to them ",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "amhil'hum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءٍ",
        "answer": "a water",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "māin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّجْمُ",
        "answer": "(It is) the star",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "al-najmu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاصِرٍ",
        "answer": "any helper",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "nāṣirin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَنْظُرِ",
        "answer": "So let see",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "falyanẓuri",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "soul",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْهَزْلِ",
        "answer": "(is) for amusement",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bil-hazli",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "86",
        "ayah": "9"
    }
]; 
export default words;